(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2 Recap Special=
(Earth Group Acting Showcase)
Hello?
Son,
(Role-play, don't take it seriously)
wait for me.
Later, I'll...
Okay, I'll talk to you later.
Is it you,
Yuwen?
What a coincidence.
Such a coincidence.
Yeah.
You now have a son?
I'll
pick him up from school later.
Are you...
I'm single.
I didn't expect time to pass so fast.
I remember back then,
we would
watch the stars
at night.
We would
think of many funny bits.
You had most ideas.
Pretty good.
Is there anything else?
Go now.
School is out now.
Take care.
Come on, buddy.
Give me a few more days.
I'm really out of cash.
I...
Can you give me a few more days?
Thank you, buddy.
Thank you.
Zhou Ye.
You are...
I'm...
I'm Xingxu.
Don't you remember me?
You...
How did you change so much?
So many years have passed.
I've grown up, I guess.
You're doing well?
Pretty well.
Good.
Good to know.
I'm also doing well. I...
You owe someone money?
You saw it?
No, I just...
My mom got sick,
so I had to
borrow some.
And then...
It's fine.
Well,
I'm in a hurry.
I can't really help you much
with this situation.
It's okay. No need for that.
Take this pair of glasses and sell them.
No.
No need. Really no need.
I'm doing fine.
I...
I can pay it back in a few days.
My job is pretty good.
It's going smoothly.
It's alright. If you're busy, go ahead.
Okay.
Bye.
Zhou Ye.
If you need anything,
just call me.
Okay.
Alright.
(Role-play, don't take it seriously)
Almost there.
Alright.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for the car, buddy.
Why are you calling me that?
For five years,
you moved to four cities,
went on seven blind dates,
and now you call me "buddy"?
I think the fifth one was pretty good.
Liu Yuning.
A bit too tall.
This is not really a coincidence.
Something happened.
Our dog...
He...
Go see him.
Maybe for the last time.
We're running out of time.
Let's run.
Or it'll be too late.
I just got a call.
Just run.
I'll be right there.
Almost there.
Wait a bit longer.
That last one, Liu Yuning.
He's from Dandong.
His family sells strawberries, right?
He's rich now.
Right?
We just didn't click.
The fourth one was good too.
Guo Jingfei.
What do you think?
I think it has nothing to do with you.
Fine.
Almost there.
Never mind.
He's gone.
Bye.
Even if he's gone,
I'm still going to see him.
Because I can't be as heartless
as you are.
I'm off.
I think
(Role-play, don't take it seriously)
you were right that day.
You said...
Come over here.
Fighting over her.
She said she doesn't want
to go with you.
I'm going to the restroom.
Wait, there's nothing between us.
Why are you leaving?
This is so weird. It's hard to explain.
Quick, sit down.
Wouldn't it be weirder if I stayed?
Who is the one jealous
to the point of madness?
I told you, there's nothing between us.
See, now he's gone,
and it's even more awkward.
I know.
I know his family is well-off.
I'm not worthy of you.
Actually, I don't know
what kind of job
I'll get after college.
I might just go back home.
He's a local here.
Being with him,
you might have a better life
than with me.
I just want to tell you
that I hope you find happiness.
Don't you love strawberries the most?
So I bought this box.
But I just had one,
and it wasn't very sweet.
I wanted you to have them.
Just be happy.
I'm leaving now.
You too.
Okay.
What's going on?
Is he playing Flash?
Slow-motion shot.
He's Flash.
Do you still remember me?
The me from 20 years ago?
Back then,
we met for the first time.
Our game was on the merry-go-round.
We danced on the platform,
just like this.
Wait...
He's using exercise
to raise his heart rate.
You know?
(Physically raising heart rate)
Now dance.
Do you remember me now?
I'm calling the police.
Yuwen, it's me.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not a creepy guy.
I haven't been stalking you.
My time is running out.
So I have to tell you quickly.
Do you remember this move?
This one.
And that little green ball?
Every time you threw it,
I would fetch it back for you.
It's me.
I miss you every day.
I've been watching you.
I want to tell you
I will always protect you.
I really have to go. Goodbye.
(Role-play, don't take it seriously)
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for the car.
What about you?
I'm
going to work.
What a coincidence.
Yeah.
What have you been up to lately?
It's still the same,
working,
spending time with my parents and stuff.
Well...
What?
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
Well, I'm also single now.
Well...
I can afford things now.
What do you mean?
I mean
the old me
couldn't really afford
anything for you.
But now
I can buy you whatever you want.
Am I that kind of person in your eyes?
No.
No, I just feel like I...
I owe you.
I didn't want anything back then.
But I wanted to give it to you.
Then why didn't you ask me?
Do you know
what I couldn't stand the most?
You just assumed everything.
You assumed
you couldn't give me what I wanted
and then just walked away.
Now, you come back assuming
you can give me what I want.
I'm sorry.
If
you can give me a chance, I think
I can do much better.
Could you?
I don't know.
How about we try?
Okay?
You've got the nerve to show up.
Are you doing well recently?
None of your business.
I saw
your new drama aired.
It's being promoted.
It's pretty sweet.
I ship you guys too.
Do you know what day yesterday was?
Yesterday was
the two-year anniversary
of our drama.
Stay away from me.
For the two-year anniversary,
I want to give you a gift.
Tap it.
♪The stars in your eyes descending♪
♪In the next second, they light me up♪
♪I deliberately appear around you♪
♪Hoping you will see me♪
♪The scene of a confession♪
♪I've imagined it a thousand times♪
♪How does the heart beat♪
♪Can't catch the time♪
♪Sweetness in the blink of an eye♪
♪I'm right in front of you♪
It's been two years.
There's something
I've always wanted to tell you.
I sing better than you.
(Role-play, don't take it seriously)
(Chen Xingxu, the domineering CEO.
Song Qian, the daughter of the rival family)
Look.
Quite beautiful, right?
(Deeply captivated)
I can't stand it.
I told you
not to bring me to France.
What if your mom finds out?
She'll be angry.
It's fine.
My dad won't find out.
(It should be "mom")
I've chartered the whole boat.
Even in a speedboat,
she couldn't catch us.
This is our secret trip.
There's no way they'll find out.
We just flew here this morning.
Right?
Now we're watching the night view.
How could she possibly know?
True.
I'm still jet-lagged.
(Waiting for entrance)
What should we do?
It's fine.
Don't worry about it.
I still think
we should buy tickets
and fly back right away.
What if they
take away your inheritance rights?
Impossible.
Alright.
Stop telling me
about your achievements.
(Did I say anything?)
I'm tired of hearing them.
I admit you're excellent.
But
I can't let you give up
your whole family for me.
It's fine.
(Good drama, love it)
You are my whole world.
Take a good look.
What are you doing?
Dad?
I'm your mom.
(Guo Jingfei,
the domineering CEO's mother)
Mom.
I'm your mom.
Although I have a bit too
much testosterone,
(Trying not to laugh)
and my hormones are a bit strong.
That's because you two infuriate me.
You didn't expect me
to come so quickly, did you?
No.
Listen to me.
This has nothing to do with her.
Get out of my way.
No.
This is absolutely because of me.
Mom.
No, I mean, ma'am.
You can't just change roles like that.
(Addressing her too soon)
She chooses to escalate the conflict.
(Totally getting it)
How many times have I told you?
Our families have a feud.
How could you be with him?
(You, him)
How can you be with him?
(Ma'am?)
(Mom?)
(Total chaos)
You're my mom.
Which path are you taking?
Aren't I the domineering CEO?
(Any problem?)
(Brilliant)
I am the domineering CEO.
(Domineering CEO's Mom)
(Mom of Domineering CEO)
(Reviewing the prompt)
A domineering CEO.
The daughter of the rival family.
(Smoothly back into character)
I've told you so many times.
How could you be with her?
Ma'am,
please don't scold him.
It's all my fault.
I'd like to ask,
what's her background?
No matter what,
no matter our feud,
she is the woman I love the most.
(True love, close to the line)
That's not what you said.
Well...
"The most"...
Not "the most".
After the last time I heard it,
I thought you and that girl
could get married right away.
How come you switched to another one?
(What plot is this?)
I didn't.
Don't listen to her nonsense.
So...
Don't explain to her yet.
Tell me first.
Back then,
(Answer the question first)
when you described that girl back then,
what kind of love was it?
(Say it boldly)
That girl you described.
True love?
Is that so?
He said she was his true love?
Right.
(Got it instantly)
Exactly.
I did say she was my true love.
(Let me interject)
Miss,
a man like him
tells every girl that same word.
Mom, you're my mom.
(Peeking at the next line)
Can you trust him?
No.
(Role-play, don't take it seriously)
(Lin Yi as martial arts couple, male
Yuwen as martial arts couple, female)
(Liu Yuning as the innkeeper, male)
Honey.
My lady.
Aha.
Shall we
eat?
(Let a tiger go)
[*Sounds like "shall we eat" in Chinese]
Back to the mountain?
(What plot is this?)
(Quickly playing along)
But we don't have...
No travel money.
(Heading toward the inn)
I want to eat something.
Let's go
to the inn.
(Friendly reminder)
Not far away, is there...
An inn?
An inn.
I don't care.
You don't care?
Then I shall quarrel.
(Both have a little temper)
If you quarrel, I shall leave home.
I shall sleep outside tonight.
Then I shall follow.
(Waiting eagerly)
Knock, knock, knock.
You two,
a quick bite or staying the night?
It's you.
(Old acquaintance, Steve,
old acquaintance)
Why are you here?
How come?
Since we parted last time...
(Who are you, sir?)
Excuse me.
Who is this?
I don't know him.
(Enjoying it)
My lady.
Aha!
Why hasn't your smile
faded since we walked in?
I'm naturally smiley.
Naturally smiley?
Then your luck can't be bad.
(Full of meme power)
Honey, I really admire your wisdom.
Do you still remember me?
I...
Of course I remember you.
You...
My Yuning.
(Hurt)
Your Yuning?
(Front-row spectators)
(Shy)
(Panicked)
Did I let it slip?
How many Yunings do you have?
(Jealous)
Yuning...
you are my true love.
[*"You" and "ning" sound alike in Chinese]
(The king of puns can't stand this)
This isn't proper, is it?
Then do you remember...
(Starting to guide the Two Fiends)
Back then...
What did the martial world call us
when we were together?
The Condor couple?
No.
Immortals...
(Denying it)
No.
(Thinking)
In the martial world,
there's a famous...
Stop talking.
Title.
Take a guess.
(Designated to answer)
That's right.
We are the Two Fiends.
You...
(Totally awesome)
(Highlight moment)
We really are the Two Fiends.
We have to make that kind of laugh.
The Two Fiends.
I sent you many letters before.
(Receiving info: sending letters)
The method I used was the most advanced
method in the martial world.
Pigeon Post?
Exactly.
(The Two Awesome Fiends)
What?
(What?)
No wonder you fed me
pigeon soup every day.
So
there's this kind of thing.
So great.
It's thrilling.
(No competition, only admiration)
(Round 1)
Come on.
(This round's performer)
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
Three,
two,
one.
Oh, my.
This is...
(Hard to judge)
You're out.
Yu Zecheng,
if you acted like this
in "Lurk",
you'd be dead
in the first episode, you know?
Don't question
(Speaking up for Honglei)
Honglei's acting,
okay?
(Supporting)
He's the top spy schemer, okay?
Top spy schemer.
It's layers upon layers of schemes.
I think you guys are doomed.
Come on.
Lin Yi,
go.
Lin Yi.
This is when your acting skills
are tested.
Rubbing it.
Turn up the strength level.
Finding the position.
Come on, get ready.
Come on.
Three, two, one.
(First time getting shocked)
(No comparison, no difference)
Our setup is that we all act fake.
(Not quite getting it)
It's my turn.
Your turn.
My turn.
He definitely won't...
He's just like that, right?
He's already like that.
Ready? Here we go.
Three, two, one.
(Think about it)
Tricky little schemer.
All right, come on.
(Game props professionally tested.
Do not imitate)
Three, two, one.
His acting looks real.
(Hard to choose)
(Go ahead and guess)
Your turn.
(Guessing Team, Round 2, Acting Team)
Rock, paper, scissors.
Leave it to fate.
(Arrangement of fate)
Let's act as fake as possible.
Okay.
(Strategy: Pass off the fake as real)
Come on.
(Focused intently)
One, two, three.
Let's act as fake as possible.
(Cheered up alone)
If
that was your real reaction just now,
your acting was so fake.
(Just what I wanted)
So you think I didn't act well?
Jingfei,
the acting was really off.
We need to deliver it directly
so the audience can clearly tell
he got shocked.
Right.
Come on.
Speed defeats all techniques.
No thinking. Come on.
One, two, three.
(Can't hold it in anymore)
You're a pro.
Why did you break character and laugh?
Still...
Still couldn't hold it back.
You sat down before getting into it.
Come on.
Come on, speed defeats all techniques.
One, two, three.
(So fake everyone is speechless)
Come on.
(Holding on)
Wow.
Can I hold up your face?
(Can't watch people I know do this)
("It Started with a Kiss")
How could it have nothing to do with me?
The person you like is me.
You can't like anyone else.
("It Started with a Kiss", Take 2)
You're always so confident.
She's about to cry.
What should you do?
My mouth.
My mouth is full of water.
Come on, do it again.
("It Started with a Kiss", Take 3)
How could it have nothing to do with me?
The person you like is me.
You can't like anyone else.
You're always so confident.
(What was the line?)
What is this?
What is this? Right.
Even I have memorized it.
You really want to act.
(Always ready)
("It Started with a Kiss", Take 4)
I do like you,
but you don't like me at all.
Don't.
Don't fall for someone else.
Come on. Get up.
Get up.
(Mesmerized and immersed)
Coming.
You two crouch down first. Yes.
Xingxu, crouch down first.
Then stand up later.
(Making room)
Right.
And then?
Kiss.
(Can't bear to look)
Then crouch down.
Then you two...
Come on.
Chaoyue, come on.
(The leads are back)
Pick it up.
Let's go home.
Okay.
Awesome.
Can we get half a point for this?
(Really need that double's pay)
Yeah, give us half a point.
You have to do the whole scene to count.
(Not hesitating for even one second)
How could it have nothing to do with me?
Come on.
The person you like is me.
Get down.
You get down.
(The stage is ours)
You're of no use anymore.
Come on.
Say it.
(Title: It Started with a Kiss
Cast: Li Naiwen, Guo Jingfei)
How could it have nothing to do with me?
Why is Fei
keeping one eye closed?
(One-eyed acting)
The person you like is me.
You can't like anyone else.
Fei is spitting water out.
Don't.
You're always so confident.
What is this even?
(Fierce counterattack)
How do you know the person I like
isn't you?
You don't like me at all.
Don't.
Don't fall for someone else.
Kiss!
(Stunned)
("Forbidden City Summit")
Ying,
you shouldn't have come.
Let's switch positions. Come on.
You take my position.
Come on.
(Smooth position switch)
Okay, come on.
Now let's dance.
Come on.
Floor moves.
Stop!
Stop fighting!
(If you're itchy, take a shower)
I beg you! Please stop!
I'll punch you.
You block me.
Okay.
(Manual slow motion)
I'll dodge.
And then,
you punch me.
Okay.
Hook.
Duck.
No!
Stop fighting!
(Stop this farce)
Okay.
The dance wasn't fierce enough.
Not fierce enough?
That wasn't fierce enough?
(Lost all energy)
That's enough.
(Scenario: Fellow disciples dueling
out of jealousy over a junior sister)
Wait, you still don't understand
that we're together already?
You two are together?
You think
the one she likes is you?
Is it you then?
Last night,
she washed my socks.
You didn't know that, did you?
Are you that close?
Wait.
She even said my socks
(More details)
had a unique fragrance.
Wait a moment.
(Just shut up)
(Anxious)
Before washing your socks,
she washed my dishes.
(Showing off)
Do you know why she washed your dishes?
Why?
She wanted to tell you
you two
are done for.
Washing dishes.
[*It sounds like "done for" in Chinese]
Washing my socks means I'm very
"wow".
[*"Socks" sounds like "wow" in Chinese]
(Amazed by his own talent)
(Totally speechless)
What a lame pun.
You're doing puns even in ancient times?
Losing to me, you don't need
to feel inferior.
Stop playing these
useless word games.
Draw your sword.
Bring it on.
(What's that?)
(What an eye-opener)
I know you had hotpot yesterday
(Creative approach)
and feel a bit unwell today.
No need for medicine anymore.
Being cut feels quite good.
Really?
You're addicted to this, huh?
Come on.
Come over here.
Junior Brother.
If you two keep this up,
your junior sister being here
won't help.
(Does anyone remember the mission?)
Right.
(Mission incoming)
Senior Brothers!
(Line 2: What is love in this world?)
Junior Sister has a message for you two.
Yesterday, you two
both said the same romantic line to her.
But she forgot the first part.
The second part was,
"It makes people willing to die for it."
It makes people
willing to die for it.
Willing to die for it.
It makes people willing to die for it.
Two...
Two uneducated people.
Nice.
Junior Brother.
(Penalizing each other with a strike)
Stop just training martial arts.
Read some books.
I've got it.
Senior Brother,
(The smart brain wins the day)
what is love in this world?
(Line 2: What is love in this world?)
Senior Brothers.
What's next?
(Action 2: Cover each other's mouths)
You've learned
an earth-shattering secret of our sect.
Now the action you need to do is...
Tell everyone.
(Human loudspeaker)
No.
We can't let outsiders know.
So you need to...
One action.
Hurry up.
(Crazy BBQ)
Don't let...
(Out of ideas)
Don't listen. It's a hate comment.
Is this right?
(Cover the mouth)
Not this?
Don't look. It's a hate comment.
Huh?
Go.
Don't move.
Together?
Huh?
A bit lower.
Shut up.
(Action 2: Cover each other's mouths)
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪That day,
we traveled together far away♪
♪In countless late nights,
we exchanged courage♪
♪Our fates have already intertwined♪
♪In each other's life trajectories♪
♪We leave behind
bonds like no other for a lifetime♪
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪Traveling around the earth♪
♪Tasting all the freshness♪
♪Having traveled all corners♪
♪We still stand shoulder to shoulder♪
♪I'm glad to have met you♪
♪We sing beautifully together♪
♪Even if we're scattered in the future♪
♪Thankfully we still share the same sky♪